It is the middle of summer in the legendary city of Grand Japan, a place known as a veritable
cornucopia of cultures from all places and times.
Everyone appears to be as energetic and heated as the Great Sun itself.
For example, this bit of commotion currently underway.
Big news, everyone!
Big news!
The Great Portable Shrine Race?
Yeah, that's right!
The whole town is talking about it!
It's the biggest news of the summer!
Is that so?
It takes place once every hundred years.
No wonder I've never heard of it.
I, for one, have heard of it.
I've also heard that the grand prize is incredible.
They say when the race is over, they present a sacred treasure from the Grand Shrine to the winner,
and then they get to make whatever wish they want!
So the treasure grants wishes, huh?
Here.
Some cold water for you.
Oh, perfect!
Just what I needed!
Ah, good stuff.
Thanks.
Uh, wait, who are you?
Our newest helping hand.
I just hired her.
I'm O'Mao.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
Seconds, please!
Sure.
Oh, right!
A heaping portion!
Good service!
You're gonna fit in just fine!
Ah!
You're me!
I'd go a little easy on the extra food for that one, O'Mao-chan.
He's just gonna put it on his never-ending tab and forget about it.
Okay.
So what is this sacred treasure you mentioned?
Oh, right.
Well, according to the legend, the sacred treasure has the magical ability to grant any wish you desire.
It's kept in the Grand Shrine's treasure room, which is only opened once a century.
One policeman supposedly had his wish granted and became a great and powerful samurai.
Another wish was made by a cook who married the prettiest girl in town and lived in complete happiness for the rest of his life.
Is that so awesome?
Right? That does sound pretty awesome.
That settles it! Let's enter the Great Portable Shrine Race!
Forget it.
I refuse to take part in some sweaty competition for some prize that's probably just a hoax.
There's also a cash prize of one million rioberries.
Come on, you guys! Get ready!
We have to win the Grand Portable Shrine Race!
Wouldn't you know, she's suddenly up for it.
Right.
And if we're going to win, the first thing we'll need is a portable shrine.
Okay.
So then, what's our first stop, Onami?
The lumber yard, of course.
The lumber yard?
I hear the greatest carpenter in all of Grand Japan lives there, and we need nothing but the best.
Hello?
There doesn't seem to be anyone here.
Huh?
What is this thing?
That's a really nice roll of fabric.
Whoops! Sorry about that.
Oh, I...
I'm glad you caught it, though. Thanks a lot, little lady.
It went flying off when I tried drying it with my special Frankie Workshop super drying clockwork mechanism.
Master Builder!
You shouldn't go out in public like that!
You've gotta cover yourself!
We got here just in time. My goodness, that was a close call.
Just in time, my ass!
You heard the ladies. I'll need that back now.
Wait, what?
That cloth.
Uh, do you mean this?
Of course I do. I mean, that is my loincloth after all.
Super, huh?
Uh-huh.
Your loincloth?
Ohh, awesome! What's this do-icky with the face?
Oh, you mean this old thing?
That's my super drying clockwork fun fan sunny wig.
Glad you like it.
That's the coolest thing ever!
His loincloth.
It landed right on my face.
So then, what kind of super portable shrine
do you want me to make for you fellas?
Well, I guess the most important thing
is that it can win the portable shrine race!
Well, yeah, that.
But it needs to look awesome, too,
so we'll look cool crossing the finish line.
Winning might be harder than we first thought.
The other teams who are participating
all sound pretty tough if you ask me.
First there are the legendary Flying Fish Riders,
the fastest gang in all of Grand Japan.
Then there's Rolling Express,
who are speedy in racing and love.
Hello there! I like you a lot!
Marry me! Marry me!
Marry me!
Looks like both of those teams have really good track records,
and those are just the ones on top of the list.
Hm?
What is the Thriller Company?
I don't know.
I've never heard of them before.
False!
False! False! False! False! False!
Ugh!
Huh?
Uh?
arter-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar-tar
Ooooo!
So who are these weirdos?
These weirdos pretty sure they're the ones you guys were just talking about the thriller company
They specialize in import and wholesale. They recently moved into a 13-story tower that was built over in the foreign district
Are you guys here to request a portable shrine for the race tomorrow too or what?
Don't be silly art was completed long ago
No, we were just stopping by to pay you a little courtesy call and tell you it's pointless for you to enter the race
It's just what exactly are you trying to imply yeah jerks. Maybe it's pointless for you to enter the race
My she's a feisty one
Just my time opinions aside. It's in your best interest to heed our advice. You don't want to get hurt
Do you shindri don't stand in front of me when I talk your threats don't scare us. We have a secret weapon
This is boss luffy a freeloading policeman in our key to victory
Hmm
Come everyone. Let's take our leave but heed my words. You'll be sorry if you dare oppose the thriller company
Hey your friends left without you thought you should know
Oh
They ditched me
All right, you have been warned
Beware
Now what was that all about geez
Oh man, what a weirdo
Of all the nerve it doesn't get much creepier
Don't worry about them. They think they can intimidate us, but they're just wasting their time. Listen up everyone
Don't you dare lose to those weird little creeps
I'm gonna build you the most super portable shrine the world has ever seen see a better win got it
We got it. You can count on us. All right guys. We gonna win this thing or what?
Yeah
Let's go
Let's go let's go let's go
Oh
I can't hear you
What's with all the racket
I'm trying to sleep here
Stop stop
That chant sucks. What are you palanquin carriers?
Sorry, sir. We couldn't think of anything else
We'll work those brains harder. There's got to be something more worthy of the flying fish riders the fastest gang in all of grand japan
Handsome handsome handsome handsome handsome
That's more like it say it again and again
At least they're leaving with their chance at my awesome face. There's no way we can lose
and then
Oh
You lovely ladies who want to kiss just form a line
Uh-huh
Oh, you couldn't lie. Oh, that's so naughty of you. Don't worry. There's enough of me to go around
You idiots. What in the hell is going on down there?
Sorry boss. It looks like we're suddenly missing four people. That's impossible count again. Everyone sound off one two
three four
six seven
Oh
See nobody's missing. We're all here
So we are
Who the hell are you?
Oh, just some zombies that were passing by
Zombies?
Hey, what did you jerks do with our friends?
Why did I act so tough?
I'm just a big loud stain on society
I just wanted someone to pay attention to me
Sorry zombies
I'm not even good enough for you to make soup out of me
Oh, you guys. Why are you so down in the dumps?
Oh
That would be because I did this
Negative
hollow
Oh
I'm depressed
Totally depressed
Extremely depressed
Boss, what's wrong?
Carrying shrines and winning stupid races
Things matter
They won't help us make it in this crazy world
This big pilot junk ain't nothing but a stinking pipe dream
It's as useless as me
Ah
Boss, please get a hold of yourself
Well, that's another one down, huh?
You
Nothing is biting
Yes, got one.
All right, now come on.
Whoa, this thing's huge.
I won't let you beat me.
There we go. Let's see what we'll do.
Boats.
Come on.
Beasts.
Help.
Help. Me.
What?
Help me, please.
Oh!
Ah!
Huh?
I don't know who he is, but he sure does eat a lot.
He sure does.
Yeah, he also doesn't know the first damn thing about table manners.
Come on, why do all of our customers suck?
You sure like to eat, huh?
Can we get some more yakitori over here?
You're no better than he is!
Here's the bill, thank you.
Where do I get it?
I must say, that was a delectable meal.
My compliments to the chef and your hospitality.
Stop it already, you swine!
Who the hell are you?
My apologies, please excuse my late introduction.
I'm Brooke, all dead and bones.
It's truly an honor to make your acquaintance, all of you.
I was born...
I was born in...
Wow, I forget, oh well.
When you introduce yourself,
you gotta get all the way to the end, not stop in the middle.
I mean, not that I care.
I know it's strange, but all I seem to remember is my name.
It's possible that some sort of traumatic shock
caused you to lose your memory.
Huh.
Hey, uh, is it just me, or is there something rattling around in your head?
That explains it, he's got a screw loose.
Huh? My, how uncouth!
You can open your skull?!
It's so awesome!
Oh, look at that, I found something.
It looks like a flute, a wooden one.
A flute?
Huh?
What the hell?!
How can you store things like that in there?!
Oh, wow!
Man, Brooke, you sure are a funny guy!
Hehehehe.
Well...
I gotta admit, it looks pretty good on you.
Hehehehe, you sure Parker пожаешь an old chick!
Hehehe.
Huh?
Ahhh!
Ohosie!
Dude!
Oh ohhh…
Ha ha ha haaa...
Hehehe, hehehe...
Hmm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss.
The flying fish riders have dropped out too.
That leaves only the Rolling Express and those imbeciles at the pinwheel eatery.
Once they're gone, victory will belong to the Thriller Company without so much as a fight.
The race is tomorrow. I think it's about time to finish this off. Let's go, Absalom.
Watch what you're ordering around. I know what to do.
Foss, foss, foss, foss, foss, foss.
Let's indulge in some dastardly deeds.
Oh, for crying out loud, Sidri. Why do you keep doing that?
Hello, everyone. Take a break and have some food.
Right. Hey, thanks for that.
Thank you.
.
Huh?
Who's taking our shrine?
No idea. I don't see anybody.
No way! It's floating!
Oh, man, I'm completely stuffed. That food was great.
Goodness, being around you makes me eat far too much.
Looking at this bill, I'm inclined to agree.
What the? How?
That shrine is flying.
Come back!
Somebody stop that thing!
After it!
Right!
Thank you! I appreciate the help! Will you marry me?
No way!
Rejection! That makes the 4,450th one!
This thing sure is heavy!
Get back here!
Stop floating, you dumb shrine!
Whoa, those guys look sick!
Damn it, we don't need this right now!
They're zombies!
Oh, no!
No!
They're
Oh, no!
So happy!
Capote, bon niveau!
Yay!
Wow, Brooke, I had no idea you were so strong.
Huh? Indeed.
I had no idea that I was so strong either.
Hey, are you all right?
What happened here?
Oh, hey, Sanji and Onami.
Who the hell are they?
Married me!
That doesn't look good.
It's over.
There's no way we can enter the big race now.
And it was such a beautiful shrine too.
I was sure my husband would be waiting for me at the finish line.
If their plan was to wipe out all the portable shrines before the race,
then that means ours is in danger too!
That would mean Omao-chan is in trouble right now.
What makes you say that?
She delivered some lunchboxes to the Frankie workshop,
but never came back.
We were headed over there to check things out.
Everybody moving! Get out of the way! Coming through!
Oh no, Chan!
Yeah!
Okay, time for John Gong!
Banzooka!
Boss Luffy! Frankie-san is...
Get Blue Nose Sensei right away!
Right!
Oh, pal, are you alright?
My head hurts if it's killing me.
My eyes have gone hazy.
Well, that is...
If I wasn't already dead, it actually had eyes.
That's a creepy thing to joke about.
Huh?
I remember what happened.
You got your memory back?
Yes.
I remember...
everything now.
Hey, what's with the hat and that get-up?
Because it looks like you're leaving.
I shouldn't be here with you, from what I remember.
And I'm ashamed to say this.
I believe that I'm actually a member of the Thriller Company.
But that can't be true!
Brook-san, no!
There you go again.
That's enough of your stupid jokes.
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
Wait!
What's with those Thriller Company guys?
And I don't mean the fact that half of them are weird animals.
I don't mean the fact that half of them are weird animals.
I mean the fact that they're all cheaters!
Yeah!
They're gonna pay!
If it's a fight they want, it's a fight they'll get!
Show them who's boss, Usopp!
Me?
No!
I'm scared!
I'm the next!
One Piece!
Feudal Era Side Story!
Defeat Thriller Company's Trash!
I'm gonna be a policeman!
What's with those Thriller Company guys?
And I don't mean the fact that half of them are weird animal things.
I mean the fact that they're all cheaters!
Yeah!
They're gonna pay!
If it's a fight they want, it's a fight they'll get!
Show them who's boss, Usopp!
Me?
No!
I'm scared!
On the next!
One Piece!
Feudal Era Side Story!
Defeat Thriller Company's Trash!
I'm gonna be a policeman!